Well, here I am floating
face-down in a swimming pool.
好吧，我漂浮在这里
在游泳池里脸朝下。
I always wanted a pool,
and in the end, I got one.
我一直想要一个游泳池，
最后，我得到了一个。
How did I get here?
我是怎么到这里的？
Well,
it all started yesterday.
嗯，
这一切都从昨天开始。
Ah.
啊。
Oh!
哦！
Sponge--
ugh!
海绵--
呃！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Whoa!
哇！
Squidward,
did you say something?
章鱼哥，
你说了什么吗？
Why are you digging up
your yard?
你为什么要挖
你的院子？
I'm putting in a pool.
我正在把它放在一个水池里。
Oh, a pool?
哦，游泳池？
Mm-hmm, and I'm going
to invite my favorite
嗯嗯，我这就去
邀请我最喜欢的
next-door neighbor
as soon as it's ready.
隔壁邻居
一旦准备好。
Get off me!
放开我！
I wouldn't be caught dead
我不会被抓死
in your muddy, little
bacteria hole.
在你的泥泞中，小
细菌孔。
I only swim
in sophisticated pools.
我只会游泳
在复杂的水池中。
Well, if you change
your mind, it's almost done.
好吧，如果你改变
你的心意，快完成了。
Yeah, sure.
是的，当然。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
It's done!
完成了！
Huh?
啊？
What the--?
什么——？
Why, it's beautiful.
为什么，它很漂亮。
Why does he get to have a pool?
他为什么要拥有一个游泳池？
If anyone around here
deserves a pool,
如果这附近有人
值得拥有一个泳池，
it's me.
这就是我。
Cannonball!
炮弹！
Oh.
哦。
Hey, Squidward,
come join us in the pool!
嘿，章鱼哥，
快来加入我们的泳池吧！
Quick,
while the water's still wet!
快点，
趁水还是湿的！
Pool!
水池！
Forget the pool.
忘记游泳池吧。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
What the--?
pool.
什么——？
水池。
Oh!
哦！
Pool!
水池！
Keep quiet,
you chlorinated clods!
保持安静，
你们这群氯化土块！
- Cannonball!
- Huh?
- 炮弹！
- 啊？
- Oh!
- Uh-oh.
- 哦！
- 呃哦。
Ouch!
哎哟!
Ow, ow.
噢，噢。
Who needs a soggy, old pool
谁需要一个又湿又旧的泳池
when you have the luxury
and elegance
当你有奢侈的时候
和优雅
of indoor air conditioning. Mwah.
的室内空调。哇。
Ooh, it's a little hot.
哦，有点热。
Huh?
啊？
That is one cool pool,
my fool.
那是一个凉爽的泳池，
我的傻瓜。
See you tomorrow, SpongeBob.
- Swim safely, Patrick.
明天见，海绵宝宝。
- 安全游泳，帕特里克。
Meet you at the pool.
在泳池遇见你。
Oh, it's so hot.
噢，太热了。
Hey, Squidward...
嘿，章鱼哥……
What?
Who said that?
什么？
谁说的？
Don't be a drip.
Take a dip.
别当滴滴。
泡一泡。
You know you want to.
你知道你想要。
SpongeBob is asleep.
海绵宝宝睡着了。
I'll just take a quick dip
to cool off.
我会快速浸泡一下
冷静下来。
That a boy!
那是个男孩！
Jump in.
跳进去。
Pool.
水池。
Oh! Oh!
哦！哦！
Thank Neptune
nobody heard me.
评分此翻译： 感谢你的评分 不好 好
没有人听到我说话。
Ah!
啊!
Gary, you leave
加里，你离开吧
those sea bunnies alone
and come to bed.
那些海兔独自一人
然后上床睡觉。
Ow!
噢！
Phew.
唷。
Now I can have the pool
all to myself.
现在我可以拥有泳池了
全部归我自己。
Oh, pool.
哦，泳池。
Ciao, everybody.
再见，大家。
all: Ciao, Squidwardo.
全体：再见，章鱼哥。
Squidwardo, you must play
your clarinet for us.
章鱼哥，你一定要玩
你的单簧管给我们。
You simply must.
你必须这么做。
I'll think about it.
我会考虑一下。
all: Aw.
全体：噢。
Ciao bella.
再见贝拉。
- Mwah.
- 哇。
Wha--
世界卫生大会 -
Egad, I must've fallen asleep.
哎呀，我一定是睡着了。
I can't let them
find me here.
我不能让他们
在这里找到我。
Ooh, I can't wait
to get wet!
哦，我等不及了
弄湿！
Hey, where's the pool toys?
嘿，泳池玩具在哪里？
Oh, not the pool shed,
not the pool shed,
哦，不是泳池棚，
不是泳池棚，
not the pool shed.
不是泳池棚。
They're in
the pool shed, silly.
他们在
泳池棚，愚蠢。
Gotta hide.
得躲起来。
- Toys, toys, toys!
- Me first! Me first!
- 玩具，玩具，玩具！
- 我先！我先！
Okay, Patrick.
好吧，帕特里克。
You can pick first.
- Hmm.
你可以先选。
- 唔。
Which toy,
which toy, which toy?
哪个玩具，
哪个玩具，哪个玩具？
Not me. Not me.
Not me.
不是我。不是我。
不是我。
I'll take this
big, ugly one.
我会接受这个
又大又丑的一个。
It's too floppy to float on.
It needs more air.
它太软了，无法漂浮。
它需要更多的空气。
Well, that ought to do it.
嗯，应该可以了。
Hey, nice find, Patrick.
嘿，不错的发现，帕特里克。
Cannon sit!
加农炮坐！
Ah!
啊!
Pool fight!
台球大战！
- Pool fight!
- A pool fight!
- 台球大战！
- Pool fight!
A pool--
一个水池——
Aw, it's broken.
噢，它坏了。
Ride the wave!
乘风破浪！
Yeah!
是的！
- Tug it back.
- Tug it forth.
- 把它拉回来。
- 向前拉。
- Tug it back.
- Tug it forth!
- 把它拉回来。
- 向前拉！
- Ow!
- Oh!
- 噢！
- 哦！
SpongeBob, watch this!
- Help me.
海绵宝宝，看这个！
- 帮我。
Black hole!
黑洞！
Wahoo!
哇呼！
Again, again!
再一次，再一次！
It's me!
I was the pool toy, you idiots!
这就是我！
我是泳池玩具，你们这些白痴！
Squidward...
章鱼哥...
that's the greatest magic trick
I've ever seen!
这是最伟大的魔术
我见过！
Yeah, let's do it again!
是的，我们再来一次吧！
Look, SpongeBob, I admit it.
听着，海绵宝宝，我承认。
I used your pool
without permission
我用过你的泳池
未经许可
because I'm really
jealous of it.
因为我真的
嫉妒它。
I want your pool chairs. I
want your pool jets.
我想要你的泳池椅。我
想要你的泳池喷头。
I want your pool noodles.
我想要你的泳池面条。
And most of all,
I want this diving board.
最重要的是，
我想要这个跳水板。
Squidward,
we're best neighbors.
章鱼哥，
我们是最好的邻居。
You can use my pool
anytime you like,
你可以使用我的泳池
任何时候只要你愿意，
day or night, you silly.
无论白天还是黑夜，你都傻了。
Aw, gee, thanks SpongeBob.
噢，天哪，谢谢海绵宝宝。
Say, how'd you like
to take a divey-wivey
说吧，你喜欢怎样
娶妻
on the boardy-woardy, hmm?
在板凳上，嗯？
Oh, no, thanks,
but I just couldn't.
哦，不，谢谢，
但我就是做不到。
Please, you must take
a dive, Squidwardo.
拜托，你一定要带
潜水吧，章鱼哥。
Huh?
啊？
I would love to take a dive.
我很想去潜水。
I was on my high school
swim team.
我当时在读高中
游泳队。
Hey, Squidward,
this ladder is adjustable.
嘿，章鱼哥，
这个梯子是可以调节的。
Do you want to go higher?
你想走得更高吗？
I love you all too!
我也爱你们大家！
Okay, I'll take that
as a yes.
好的，我会接受的
作为一个是。
Crank it up, Patrick!
加把劲，帕特里克！
Ciao bella!
I dive!
再见贝拉！
我潜水！
Troppo elevato!
Too high, too high!
Troppo 电梯！
太高了，太高了！
Oh, it's too high, Patrick.
Crank it down!
噢，太高了，帕特里克。
把它降下来！
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Huh?
啊？
What was that?
那是什么？
Uh, uh... hmm.
呃，呃……嗯。
Ah.
啊。
Oh.
哦。
Aw, hm.
Uh-huh?
噢，嗯。
嗯？
Ah.
啊。
- Yay!
- Yeah!
- 耶！
- 是的！
Perfect dive, Squidward.
完美的潜水，章鱼哥。
And that's how I got here.
我就是这样来到这里的。
Typical.
典型的。